Morteza Shoushtari

Graduate Research Assistant shoushtari.morteza@live.com Number: +1 (385) 450-9843

Webiste

Linkedin profile

SUMMARY

I am a Ph.D. student in the department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE), Brigham Young University. Currently, I am working on physical layer security, and secure error-correction coding. I received an M.Sc. degree in Information Technology from Shiraz University, Iran, in 2013, and I have around 6 years of work experience as an IT administrator and network engineer in big companies such as Huawei Technologies Co. and JYAN Construction Co.

RESEARCH INTERESTS

- Computer Networks
- Cloud Computing
- Physical Layer Security
- Security/Error-Correction Coding

EDUCATION

Ph.D., Computer Engineering

Dissertation topic: Secrecy in Caching Channels **Brigham Young University**, Utah, USA

• Years: 2019 - 2023 (expected)

• GPA: 3.74/4

M.Sc., Information Technology (IT) Shiraz University, Shiraz, IRAN

Years: 2011 - 2013GPA: 3.69/4

B.Sc., Computer Engineering

Sadjad University of Technology, Mashhad, IRAN

Years: 2006 - 2010GPA: 3.47/4

PUBLICATION

- Willie Harrison and Morteza Shoushtari, "On Caching with Finite Blocklength Coding for Secrecy over the Binary Erasure Wiretap Channel" in Proceedings of IEEE Wireless Telecommunications Symposium (WTS), (San Francisco, US), Apr. 2021.
- Morteza Shoushtari and Willie Harrison, "New Dual Relationships for Error-Correcting Wiretap Codes" in Proceedings of IEEE International Symposium on Information Theory (ISIT), (Melbourne, Australia), July. 2021.

Work Experiences

Brigham Young University, UTAH, USA

Jan 2019 - present

Graduate Research Assistant

• RA with the emphasize on physical layer security and coded-caching

${\bf IT\ Dep.\ HUAWEI\ Company,\ Tehran,\ Iran}$

Aug 2016 - Aug 2017

IT Administrator

• Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues

- Provided 24*7 level one support over 850 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences
- Strong contribution in Huawei IT department in Middle-East region

IT Dep. JYAN Company, Tehran, Iran

Jan 2016 - Aug 2016

Network Engineer

- Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24*7 level one support over 180 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences

IT Dep. Persia Cloud Company, Tehran, Iran Jun 2015 - Jan 2016 Network Engineer

- Installed and configured 2X and IIRAS cloud platforms (IIAS, PAAS)
- Installed and configured Microsoft Servers (CRM, SharePoint, Lync)

IT Dep. LOTUS Company, Tehran, Iran

Nov 2013 - Jun 2015

Website Developer

• Programmed and maintained company's website (lotuslaptop.com)

IT Dep. KARMA Engineering Company, Iran Technical Support

Nov 2011 - Nov 2013

- Maintained communication networks, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24*7 level one support over 50 clients
- Installed and configured technical software

Members and Honors

- Member of IEEE Communication Society (ComSoc).
- Member of IEEE Information Theory Society (ITSoc).
- Member of IEEE Electrical and Computer Engineering Honor Society, Eta Kappa Nu.
- Outstanding IT engineer in Huawei Technologies Company -2017.
- Monthly star engineer in JYANE Company-2016.
- Ranked 6th among graduate students studying IT at Shiraz University with an overall GPA of 3.7/4 (Out of 35)

CERTIFICATES AND • IT Certificates: SKILLS

- - o CompTIA A+
 - o CompTIA Network+
 - o CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate)
 - o MCITP (Microsoft Certified IT Professional)
 - o HCNA (Huawei Certified Network Associate)
- Skills in computer networks:
 - o Install and configure network devices (Switch, routers, ...)
 - o Install and configure virtual networks with VMware ESX, VCenter
 - o Knowledge in Cloud Computing Architecture such as AWS, 2x (Parallels)
 - o Network troubleshooting
- Technical knowledge:
 - o Programming Language: C/C++/Python/Matlab/Web Programming

- o Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows Client-Server/Linux
- o Software development methodology: Scrum/RUP

Language Skills Persian - Native

English - Fluent Spanish - Basic